Patrick Francis Waters

4450 S. Hualapai Way. Suite 1185 Las Vegas, NV 89147 (702) 518-1416 patrickfwaters@gmail.com

Mission Statement:

I am a dedicated, fast learning, hardworking, and experienced problem solver. My expertise in desktop, help desk and network service also comes with a substantial background of white-glove, Executive level customer service. I am extremely motivated and have the ability to accomplish many tasks simultaneously. In addition to the aforementioned, I have experience in call center work, computer hardware and software repair, personnel management and training, as well as project management.

Skills:

- Apple Concierge
- SAAS Specialist
- Okta, JIRA, Confluence, Slack Expertise
- GSuite Roll Out Team Lead at Genentech
- Executive Support Specialist
- Tier I, II, III Specialist
- Network +, A+ Certified
- iOS Support
- Windows 10, 7, XP support
- Active Directory
- Migration Specialist
- · Cisco, Netgear experience
- Proficient in Spanish
- Type 50+ WPM
- Photographic memory
- Direct administration of Windows, Mac, and Linux mixed environments.

Education:

Heald College, San Francisco, CA

2009 - 2011

Bachelor's in Applied Science Degree in Information Technology

Professional Experience:

Remote Network Administrator Rocket Lawyer

Feb 2021 - September 2021

- Mac Desktop Support
- Mac + Windows Software integration
- User Creation and Maintenance
- Executive Support

Remote Network Administrator Grocery Outlet

May 2020 - November 2020

- Mac Support
- Network Maintenance
- Router and Switch Remediation
- DVR + Network Security implementation

System Administrator Alluma, Oakland CA

Aug 2019 – May 2020

- Sole Apple Specialist
- Sole Oakland IT Professional
- Network and Endpoint Upgrades
- Active Directory and Windows 10 Tier I and II support

System Administrator Bracket/Signant Health SF, CA Jan 2019 – Aug 2019 • Contract for relocation

- Assisted in Desktop to Laptop Migrations
- Assisted in Office Relocation and Employee Introductions
- Active Directory and Windows 10 Tier I and II support

Lead Admin The Luxarium,

2016 - 2020

- Provide technical support to several small business and Executive Clients
- iPhone interoperability specialist
- Primarily Apple environments
- Deployed TeamViewer to provide remote support

System Administrator SEIU Local 1021, Oakland

2011 - 2016

- Mac/Windows all-in-one troubleshooting and repair guru
- iPhone, iPad, Macbook Czar
- Oversaw creation of and deployment of system images
- Aided in forced transition from in-house Exchange to AWS to Office365

Consultant Fixswift Inc, San Francisco

2011

- Provided remote and in-person support
- Supported mobile devices such as iPhone, iPad and Android devices
- In-depth Troubleshooting for Windows and Mac based systems

2010

Consultant Right Brain Corp, on behalf of Genentech, S. San Francisco

- Provided Tier I,II,III support to end users
- Provided interoperability support for iPhones, Macbooks, HP laptops
- Handled service calls over the phone and in-person

Technical Analyst Intern PC World, San Francisco, CA

2009 - 2010

- Troubleshooting analyst
- Batch scripted benchmarking processes
- Hardware repairs/maintenance on Macs and PCs

References:

Available upon request